<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!DOCTYPE book
  PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.2//EN"
         "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.2/docbookx.dtd" >
<book role="user">
  <title>Cúram Book</title>


  <bookinfo>


    <copyright>
      <year>2005</year>
      <holder>Cúram Software Limited</holder>
    </copyright>


    <productname class="trade">
      <trademark class="registered">Cúram</trademark> 4.0
    </productname>


    <legalnotice>
      <para>
        No part of this publication may be stored in a retrieval
        system, transmitted, or reproduced in any way, including
        but not limited to photocopy, photograph, magnetic or
        other record, without the prior agreement and written
        permission of Cúram Software Ltd.
      </para>
      <para>
        The information in this book is distributed on an
        <quote>as is</quote> basis, without warranty. While every
        precaution has been taken in the preparation of this book,
        neither the authors nor Cúram Software Ltd. shall have any
        liability to any person or entity with respect to any
        liability, loss or damage caused or alleged to be caused
        directly or indirectly by instructions contained in this
        book or by the computer software or hardware products
        described herein.
      </para>
      <para>
        Cúram is a registered trademark of Cúram Software Ltd.
        All Cúram products and service names are trademarks and
        property of Cúram Software Ltd. All Rights Reserved. All
        third-party logos, products and service names are
        property of their respective owners.
      </para>
    </legalnotice>


  </bookinfo>


  <chapter>


    <title>Introduction</title>


    <section>


      <title>Introduction</title>


      <para>
        This is the introduction to this book.
      </para>


    </section>


    <section>


      <title>Prerequisites</title>


      <para>
        These are the prerequisites for the reader of this book.
      </para>


    </section>


  </chapter>


  <chapter>


    <title>Topic</title>


    <section>


      <title>Objective</title>


      <para>
        This is the objective of this chapter.
      </para>


    </section>


    <section>


      <title>Prerequisites</title>


      <para>
        These are the prerequisites for the reader of this chapter.
      </para>


    </section>


    <section>


      <title>Introduction</title>


      <para>
        This is the introduction to the topic covered by this chapter.
      </para>


    </section>


    <section>


      <title>Details</title>


      <para>
        These are the details for this topic.
      </para>


    </section>


  </chapter>


</book>
